Think fast. Drive faster.
Overdrive is a thriller, action, mystery film directed by Antonio Negret.
Master car thieves square off against French gangsters in the South of
France with money, women and lives all on the line.
Andrew Foster, played by Scott Eastwood.
Garrett Foster, played by Freddie Thorp.
Stephanie, played by Ana de Armas.
Devin, played by Gaia Weiss.
Max Klemp, played by Clemens Schick.
Jacomo Morier, played by Simon Abkarian.
Overdrive is a 2017 action thriller film directed by Antonio
Negret and written by Michael Brandt and Derek Haas.
An international co-production of France, Belgium and the United States, the film stars Scott
Eastwood, Freddie Thorp, Ana de Armas, Gaia Weiss, Simon Abkarian and Clemens Schick.
Principal photography began on 4 January 2016 in Paris and Marseille, France.
Andrew and Garret Foster, half-brothers and skilled car thieves, are sent to steal a
crime lord's luxury car, and get more than what they bargained for.
The film was first released in theaters on June
15, 2017 and was a box office bomb.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.